Dayenne Caroline de Souza

Curitiba, PR - Brazil 25 years old. +55 41 99741 5285 day.carol18@gmail.com github.com/dayesouza

Who am I

Currently working as a FullStack Developer, with focus on UI, with knowledge on User Experience. Always studying more about new tendencies in technology and trying to do my best. Series and books lover, travelling the world is also a passion.

Education

Bachelor in Computer Information Systems – Universidade Positivo, 2017

Professional Experience

Company: ExxonMobil (since March 2019 until now)

Role: Full Stack Developer

Activities: Create mockups and get user feedback, develop responsive and intuitive UI from mockups, changing the Interface based on user feedback, developing secure REST APIs to interact with the screen, defining a new technology stack after reviewing business processes, presenting projects to the managers, participating in workshops to understand new requirements.

Front-end: ReactJS, Redux, Angular, Bootstrap, Sass, CSS, VS Code, Adobe XD, PWA;

Back-end: .NET Framework/Core and Node.JS. Technologies: GIT, Scrum, CI/CD on Azure.

Company: System FAEP - Agriculture Federation of Parana State and Senar/PR (since October 2015 until March 2019)

Role: Full Stack Developer

Activities: Developed systems based on business and user feedback, understanding requirements and discussing how to improve the whole process. Ability and freedom to bring old processes that were delivered by paper to the web, increasing the analysis and user interaction with a diversity of areas of the company. Developing systems with PHP, SQL, Javascript, CSS, HTML, Angular, and deploying them to Linux servers.

Company: HSBC Bank (October 2014 until August 2015)

Role: Developer Intern

Activities: Participation in many courses that helped me to understand and use the bank tools of development, like COBOL, their database DB2, EasyTrieve and JCL, and Microsoft Office Excel, to help with incident control.

Company: RicTV (July 2013 until September 2014)

Role: Technical Support Intern

Activities: Change of computes pieces, install and test new tools to improve the performance at Apple

and Windows computers.

Skills

I work with Angular and React in personal projects, and I'm always studying new front-end technologies, since I know they`re always changing.

- Study of UI/UX and implementation with Adobe XD;
- Azure Cloud;
- Develop responsive websites with frameworks like Angular or React, with CSS, Sass and/or Bootstrap;
- NoSQL Database with Firebase/Firestore or MongoDB, and SQL Database with Mysql and SQLServer;
- NodeJS for backend or .NET.
- Secure APIs with OAuth authentication

Languages

Portuguese: Native; **English:** Fluent.